Single dad, no clue. Single mom, flying solo.
Blended is a comedy, romance film directed by Frank Coraci.
Recently divorced mom Lauren and widowed dad Jim let their friends push
them into a blind date, which goes disastrously wrong.
Unsurprisingly, neither wants to see the other ever again.
However, fate intervenes when both Jim and Lauren, unbeknownst to each other, purchase one-half of
the same vacation package at a South African resort for families, during spring break.
They and their children are forced to share the same romantic suite and
participate in a slew of family activities together.
Jim, played by Adam Sandler.
Lauren, played by Drew Barrymore.
Eddy, played by Kevin Nealon.
Nickens, played by Terry Crews.
Jen, played by Wendi McLendon-Covey.
Hilary, played by Bella Thorne.
Blended is a 2014 American romantic comedy film starring Adam Sandler and Drew Barrymore as two single
parents who went on a blind date together and never wanted to see each other again afterwards.
To their surprise, they both end up at the same African safari resort
with their children and are forced to stay together.
The film was directed by Frank Coraci, and written
by Ivan Menchell and Clare Sera.
The film's ensemble cast also features Kevin Nealon,
Terry Crews, and Wendi McLendon-Covey.
The film was produced by Adam Sandler, Jack Giarraputo, and Mike Karz.
It was released theatrically on May 23, 2014.
grossed $128 million worldwide, against a budget of $40 million, and
received generally negative reviews from critics.
This is the third collaboration between Sandler and Barrymore after The
Wedding Singer (also directed by Coraci) and 50 First Dates.
The film explores themes of single parent, baseball,
extreme sports, safari, south africa.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.